{
    "questions": [
        {
        "subject":"General Knowledge",
        "question":"What is the worldâ€™s largest land mammal?",
        "answer1":"Colossal Squid",
        "answer2":"Blue Whale",
        "answer3":"Elephant",
        "answer4":"Hippopotamus",
        "correctAnswer":"3"

        },
        {
        "subject":"General Knowledge",
        "question":"Rio de Janeiro is a city in which South American country?",
        "correctAnswer":"Brazil",
        "possibleAnswers":["Peru", "colombia", "Argentina"]

        },
        {
        "subject":"General Knowledge",
        "question":"Which Middle Eastern city is also the name of a type of artichoke?",
        "correctAnswer":"Jerusalem",
        "possibleAnswers":["Yemen", "Cyprus", "Qatar"]

        },
        {
        "subject":"General Knowledge",
        "question":"With which sport is Silverstone most associated?",
        "correctAnswer":"Motor Racing",
        "possibleAnswers":["Triathlon", "Cycling", "Running"]

        },
        {
        "subject":"General Knowledge",
        "question":"Nostradamus was famous for making what?",
        "correctAnswer":"Predictions",
        "possibleAnswers":["Candles", "Poems", "Buildings"]

        },
        {
        "subject":"General Knowledge",
        "question":"In mythology, Romulus and Remus were brought up by which animal?",
        "correctAnswer":"Wolf",
        "possibleAnswers":["Bear", "Dog", "Ape"]

        },
        {
        "subject":"General Knowledge",
        "question":"What is the main source of vitamin C?",
        "correctAnswer":"Fruits",
        "possibleAnswers":["Sun light", "Vegetables", "Coffee"]

        },
        {
        "subject":"General Knowledge",
        "question":"Insulin is commonly used to treat which condition?",
        "correctAnswer":"Diabetes",
        "possibleAnswers":["Common Cold", "Chlamydia", "Flu"]

        },
        {
        "subject":"General Knowledge",
        "question":"The first atom bomb was dropped on which Japanese city?",
        "correctAnswer":"Hiroshima",
        "possibleAnswers":["Nagasaki", "Okinawa", "Fukuoka"]

        },
        {
        "subject":"General Knowledge",
        "question":"",
        "correctAnswer":"",
        "possibleAnswers":["", "", ""]

        }
    ]
}